A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
A Guide to the Records of the Public Library Development Division of the Virginia State Library and Archives, 1920-1992
The Library of Virginia
Accession 35467
60.5 cubic feet (173 boxes)
Virginia State Library and Archives
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred 8/7/1997 by the Public Library Development Division.
Biographical Information
The Public Library Development Division began as the Extension Divison of the Virginia State Library in 1922 with the goal of establishing new libraries in counties that did not yet have library services and enlarging already existing library systems. The division also assisted local and regional authorities in the acquisition and operation of bookmobiles. In 1942 the Virginia General Assembly appropriated money for grants in aid to localities to establish libraries and in 1956 Congress passed the Library Services Act, which provided funds to expand library services to rural areas. The Extension Division administered the distribution of both the state and federal funds.
The Virginia State Library reorganized in 1968 and the Extension Division was renamed the Library Development Branch and was given additional responsibility for cooperation, consultation and coordination within the public library network of the State. The Branch divided the State into four consultive areas and hired a consultant for each region.
The Virginia State Library was renamed the Virginia State Library and Archives in 1987 and the Public Library Development Branch became the Public Library Development Division.
Scope and Content
These files document the work of the Public Library Development Division at the Virginia State Library Archives to establish new public libraries and strengthen existing systems within the state, consult and coordinate with the public library network in the state, and distribute state and federal aid.
Records include Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992; Consultant files, 1968-1987; and Scrapbooks, 1910-1971.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992
Series II. Public Library Consultant files, 1968-1987
Series III. Scrapbooks, 1910-1970
Contents List
- Series I. Director's correspondence and subject files, 1920-1992., Extent: 45.15 cubic feet (129 boxes). (Box 1-129)
  This series is housed in 129 boxes and is arranged alphabetically within each subseries. The Director's correspondence and subject files are divided into eight sub-series: Public library files, 1920-1971; Public library files, 1971-1986; General correspondence, 1941-1965; General correspondence, 1966-1977; Public Library Consultant reports, 1979-1987; Public Library Consultant files, 1972-1986; Subject files, 1928-1989; and Lonesome Pine Regional Library JLARC study files, 1990-1992.
  Public library files, 1920-1986, consist of 80 boxes are are arranged alphabetically by the name of the library or the locality (if no public library exists). Files include incoming and outgoing correspondence and reports of the Division/Branch director to/from the various public libraries throughout the state, dealing with library establishment and development and funding issues. These files were mainttained as two separate file sequences, 1920-1971 and 1971-1986.
  General correspondence, 1941-1977, consists of 6 boxes and is arranged alphabetically, and chronologically thereunder. Includes the director's correspondence with various individuals and entities, and with public library consultants. These files were maintained in two separate file sequences, 1941-1965 and 1966-1977.
  Public Library Consultant reports, 1979-1987, consist of two boxes and are arranged alphabetically, and chronologically thereunder. Includes both quarterly and annual reports received from Public Library Consultants. Reports include general comments, consultant statistics, and information on district activities, meetings, conferences, workshops, automation, children's services, continuing education classes, film collection, grants, institutional libraries, state and federal aid, and summer reading programs.
  Public Library Consultant files, 1972-1986, consist of 5 boxes and are arranged by topic. These consultant files contain District/Area files, general files, and files for specific consultants. Files include correspondence between the Library Development Director and public library consultants, courtesy copies of consultant's correspondence with public libraries, library boards, local officials (planning district commissioners, city/county administrators, school superintendents, etc.); consultant meeting notes to file; and reports. Topics include automation, budgets, building needs, conferences, new library service, policies, procedures, regional library systems, standards, statistics, state/federal aid and workshops.
  Subject files, 1928-1989, consist of 29 boxes and are arranged alphabetically by topic. These files contain information on various topics, including associations, conferences, legislation, services, standards, statistics, and also include runs of several library publications. Subject files include correspondence, brochures, clippings, newletters, press releases, reports and speeches.
  The Lonesome Pine Regional Library JLARC study files, 1982-1990, consist of 7 boxes and are arranged alphabetically. Contains files related to an administrative audit and management review by the Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission into the Lonesome Pine Regional Library and incudes reports, statistics, clippings, manuals and notes. These files are arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Public Library files, 1920-1971.
    This sub-series consists of 48 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by the name of the public library or by the locality if no public library exists, and in reverse chronological order thereunder.
    - Accomac County - See Eastern Shore Public Library, 1941-1971.
    - Albemarle County - See McIntire Public Library, 1945-1971.
    - Alexandria Public Library, 1964-1970. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alexandria Public Library, 1949-1963. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alexandria Public Library, 1945-1948. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alleghany County - See Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1941-1971.
    - Amelia County, 1945-1970. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1967-1969. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1966. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1965. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1964. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1956-1963. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Amherst County Public Library, 1946-1955. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Appomattox Public Library, 1940-1963. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1966-1971. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1960-1965. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1955-1959. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1953-1954. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1951-1952. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1950. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1948-1949. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Arlington County Public Library, 1945-1947. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Augusta County, 1966-1971. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bath County, 1959-1970. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Bedford Public Library, 1960-1971. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bedford Public Library, 1941-1959. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Benjamin P. Chapman Memorial Library (Smithfield), 1959-1972. (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Botetour-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1966-1971. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1961-1965. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1956-1960. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1953-1956. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1950-1951. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1948-1949. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1947. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1946. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Botetourt-Rockbridge Regional Library, 1942-1945. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1957-1964. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bristol Public Library, 1945-1953. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1968-1971. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1963-1964. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1959-1962. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1956-1958. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1951-1955. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1950. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1949. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Brunswick-Greensville Regional Library, 1941-1948. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1968. (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1966-1967. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1964-1965. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1963. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1962. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Buchanan County Public Library, 1960-1961. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 1969-1971. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 1968. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 1967. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 19. (Box 6)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 1961-1966. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 1942-1957. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Campbell County Public Library (See also Patrick Henry Memorial Library), 19. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Caroline County - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library and Pumunkey Regional Library, 1945-1971.
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1971. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1970. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1969. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1968. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1967. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1965-1966. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1962-1964. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Caroline County), 1960-1966. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Spotsylvania County), 1945-1965. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Wallace Library - Fredericksburg), 1945-1955. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Wallace Library - Fredericksburg), 1958-1961. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Central Rappahannock Regional Library (Westmoreland County), 1959-1965. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1967-1971. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1965-1966. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1962-1964. (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1960-1961. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1956-1959. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1951-1955. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Charles P. Jones Memorial Library (Alleghany County), 1945-1950. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1967-1970. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1965-1966. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1960-1964. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1949-1959. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library (Hampton), 1945-1948. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Charlotte County Free Library, 1951-1971. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Charlotte County Free Library, 1945-1949. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1966-1968. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1963-1965. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1961-1962. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Public Library, 1956-1960. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1971. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1967-1970. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1962-1966. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Chesterfield County Public Library, 1942-1961. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Colonial Heights - Violet Banks Library, 1967-1970. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Community Library (Kilmarnock), 1965-1971. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Community Library (Kilmarnock), 1961-1964. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Covington - See Charles P. Jones Memorial Library, 1945-1971.
    - Craig County Public Library, 1947-1966. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Culpeper Town and Country Library, 1965-1971. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Culpeper Town and Country Library, 1956-1964. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Culpeper Town and Country Library, 1941-1955. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Cumberland County, 1947-1970. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Danville Public Library, 1965-1971. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Danville Public Library, 1961-1964. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Danville Public Library, 1958-1960. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Danville Public Library, 1956-1957. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Danville Public Library, 1955. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Danville Public Library, 1953-1954. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Danville Public Library, 1950-1952. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Danville Public Library, 1945-1949. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Dickenson County - See Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1946-1971.
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1966-1971. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1963-1965. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1961-1962. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1960. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1959. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1958. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1957. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1957. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1956. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1953-1955. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1952. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1950-1951. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1949. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Shore Public Library (Accomac County and Northampton County), 1941-1948. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Edinburg Community Library, 1969-1971. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Essex County Library, 1957-1970. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Essex County Library, 1941-1955. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1969-1971. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1968. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1966-1967. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1964-1965. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1963. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1962. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1960-1961. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1958-1959. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1955-1957. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1953-1954. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1951-1952. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1947-1950. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Fairfax County Public Library, 1941-1946. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Fairfax County Public Library - Annual Reports, 1957-1966. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Fairfax County Public Library - Vienna Library Association, 1960-1962. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1967-1971. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1965-1966. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1960-1964. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1957-1959. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1955-1956. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1951-1955. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Falls Church Public Library, 1945-1950. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Farmville Public Library, 1962-1971. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Farmville Reading Room, 1965-1971. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Farmville Reading Room, 1958-1964. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Fauquier Public Library (formerly Warrenton Public Library), 1964-1966. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Fauquier Public Library (formerly Warrenton Public Library), 1967-1971. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Fauquier Public Library (formerly Warrenton Public Library), 1957-1963. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Floyd County, 1957-1968. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County, 1947-1969. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Franklin, City of - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1941-1971.
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library, 1968-1970. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library, 1963-1967. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library, 1956-1962. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library, 1954-1955. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library - Patrick County Library, 1951-1954. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library - Patrick County Library, 1941-1950. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library - Franklin County Library, 1945-1947. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library - Franklin County Library, 1948-1951. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Franklin-Patrick Regional Library - Franklin County Library, 1945-1947. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Frederick County, 1961. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Fredericksburg, City of - See Central Rappahannock Regional Library, 1945-1971.
    - Front Royal - See Samuels Public Library, 1958-1971.
    - Galax Public Library, 1963-1971. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Giles County Library - See also Narrows Public Library, 1957-1961. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Gloucester Public Library, 1941-1969. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Goochland County, 1964-1973. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1967-1971. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1962-1966. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1959-1961. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1957-1958. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1955-1956. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1948-1954. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Halifax-South Boston Regional Library, 1938-1947. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Hampton - See Charles H. Taylor Memorial Library, 1945-1977.
    - Handley Library (Winchester), 1966-1970. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Handley Library (Winchester), 1962-1965. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Handley Library (Winchester), 1954-1961. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Handley Library (Winchester), 1945-1953. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Hanover County - See Pamunkey Regional Library, 1941-1970.
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1970-1971. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1956-1969. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1953-1955. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Henrico County Public Library, 1943-1952. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Henry County - See also Martinsville Memorial Public Library, 1950-1973. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Henry Hungerford Library - See also Westmoreland County, 1963-1966. (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Highland County, 1950-1959. (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hopewell - See Maude Langhorne Nelson Library, 1941-1971.
    - Irvington Public Library - See also Lancaster County, 1964-1969. (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Isle of Wight County - See Walter Cecil Rawls Library, 1941-1971.
    - Jones Memorial Library - See also Lynchburg Public Library, 1959-1971. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Jones Memorial Library - See also Lynchburg Public Library, 1945-1958. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Kilmarnock - See The Community Library, 1961-1971.
    - King and Queen County, 1958-1965. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - King George County - See Lewis Egerton Smoot Memorial Library, 1955-1973.
    - King William County - See Pamunkey Regional Library, 1941-1970.
    - Lancaster County Public Library - See also The Community Library, 1954-1965. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Lewis Egerton Smoot Memorial Library (King George County), 1968-1973. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lee County - See Lonesome Pine Regional Library, 1946-1971.
    - Leesburg - See Thomas Balch Library, 1963-1970.
    - Lewis Egerton Smoot Memorial Library (King George County), 1955-1967. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1970-1971. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1969. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1967-1968. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1965-1966. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1964. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County, Lee County, Wise County), 1946-1964. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County), 1963-1968. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County), 1963. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County), 1962. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Dickenson County), 1950-1961. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Lee County), 1967-1971. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Lee County), 1966. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Lee County), 1965-1966. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Lee County), 1965. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1963. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1962. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1961. (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1960. (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Lonesome Pine Regional Library (Wise County), 1959-1960. (Box 21, Folder 6)